CURRICULUM VITAE

ASWATH PRAVEEN S

Murugan koil street, Sethiyathope (Post), Bhuvanagiri (TK), Cuddalore (DT), Pincode - 608702.

Email id: Aswathpraveen30@gmail.com

Mobile No: 8122320022

OBJECTIVE

SAP professional, with 3 years of experience in the IT and Manufacturing Industry. Skilled at designing, implementing & deploying SAP solutions to achieve defined business goals. Proven record of designing, developing and delivering data warehouse and reporting solutions using SAP BW module. Possess sound knowledge of the business process and best practices to configure and integrate the SAP MM module with other functional modules

EXPERIENCE

- ➤ Process developer (SAP MM) in Genpact, Bengaluru, India (01-02-2024 to At present)
- ➤ Senior Process Executive in Infosys Limited, Bengaluru, India (05-07-2022 to 30-01-2024)
- Managment Trainee in Youngshin Automotive India PVT LTD (11-12-2019 to 21-02-2020)
- ➤ Graduate Engineer Trainee in JM Fritech India PVT LTD (23-09-2019 to 01-11-2019)

EDUCATION QUALIFICATION

- ➤ Bachelor of Engineering (2019) from Jeppiaar Institute of Technology Chennai with 6.5 CGPA.
- ➤ **Deplomo in Mechanical Engineering** (2015) from Sri Venkadachalapathy Polytechnic college (2015), Sethiyathope with **71.25%** marks.

SKILLS

- > SAP MM
- > SAP PP
- Oracle ERP
- ➤ MS Excel
- > Power point Customer Master File

PROJECT DONE

> CDW and NTT DATA

• Participated in workshops with clients to blueprint business requirements.

- Configured enterprise data structures including plants, storage locations, purchasing organizations, and purchasing groups.
- Managed MM master data configuration, covering Material Master, Vendors, Purchase Info Record, Source List, and Outline Agreements.
- Set up new document types and number ranges for Purchasing documents with release processes.
- Configured pricing procedures.
- Collaborated with other module consultants to integrate MM functionalities with FI for Valuation and Account Determination.
- Configured output messages using Smart Forms for RFQ and PO.
- Prepared core functional test scenarios and test scripts.
- Provided day-to-day post-production support.
- Assisted the client in source-to-Pay (S2P) processes.
- Managed tickets and tasks, ensuring timely closure within defined SLAs.
- Resolved user queries based on priority levels.
- Interacted with the client for ticket clarification

> ARROW intelligent solution

- Verify the quote exists in the system and meets the requirements to be converted to an order.
- Creating new pick ship, drop ship, and VAS order.
- Working on sales orders of the customers & keeping record of every transaction of the sales order.
- Tracking the ship information & keeping track of it till it reaches customer & confirming the same to the client by getting proof of delivery. Maintenance of Vendor accounts by using oracle application- Customer Master.
- Creating new vendor account, New Billing and Shipping accounts.
- Allocating Shipping Method, Carrier, freight terms and Warehouse codes.
- Providing process training to new team members.
- Preparing weekly and monthly reports using tools like Power BI, CITRIX, and MERC portals.
- Ensured all queries were addressed through e-mails so that client relationships were maintained.
- Sales order creation, order booking and management.
- Updating Existing Bill to and Ship to sites.
- Updating payment terms for the customer account.
- Handling multiple process.
- Communicating the updates of the process to the team.
- PO placement RWB Release work bench.
- Push out need to push the NBD according to customer ON HOLD.
- Pull In improving the NBD (Within 10 days no need action) Change to small, awaiting supplier, internal requisition. PO entry date.10 business days (ON HOLD). Business days not sat and sun, PO placed recent date.(tracker).
- Cancel Canceling the orders as per sales request ON HOLD

- RMA creation, Invoice attachment, order booking, CM finalization.
- POD process daily report.
- Tracking DHL portal Kart report.
- EIP- orders Reports.

STRENGTHS

- > Smart worker
- > can work efficiently under pressure.
- Helping tendency.

DATE:

PLACE:

DECLARATION	
➤ I here by declare that the information for	furnished above is true to the best of my knowledge.
DATE:	Signature

(ASWATH PRAVEEN S)